Guide to the University of Chicago Contemporary Chamber Players Records 1958-2002
University of Chicago Library
- Series XIV: Audio and Video
  - Item 10-11: CDs, January 22, 1971 performance (Box 44)
  - Item 12: CD, March 5, 1971 performance (Box 44)
  - Item 13: CD, April 23, 1971 performance (Box 44)
  - Item 14: CD, May 21, 1971 performance (Box 44)
  - Item 15: CD, January 14, 1972 performance (Box 44)
  - Item 16: CD, January 15, 1972 seminar (Box 44)
  - Item 17: CD, January 21, 1972 performance (Box 44)
  - Item 18: CD, March 3, 1972 performance (Box 44)
  - Items 19-20: CDs, April 14, 1972 performance (Box 44)
  - Item 21: CD, May 26, 1972 performance (Box 44)
  - Item 22: CD, January 26, 1973 performance (Box 44)
  - Item 23: CD, February 24, 1973 performance (Box 44)
  - Item 24: CD, March 2, 1973 performance (Box 44)
  - Item 25: CD, March 6, 1973 performance (Box 44)
  - Items 26-27: CDs, April 8, 1973 performance (Box 44)
  - Item 28: CD, April 13, 1973 performance (Box 44)
  - Items 1-2: CD, May 25, 1973 performance (Box 45)
  - Item 3: CD, January 28, 1974 performance (Box 45)
  - Item 4: CD, February 21, 1974 performance (Box 45)
  - Item 5: CD, March 8, 1974 performance (Box 45)
  - Items 6-7: CDs, April 21, 1974 performance (Box 45)
  - Item 8: CD, December 7, 1974 performance (Box 45)
  - Item 9: CD, January 24, 1975 performance (Box 45)
  - Item 10: CD, March 7, 1975 performance (Box 45)
  - Items 11-12: CDs, April 11, 1975 performance (Box 45)
  - Item 13: CD, May 30, 1975 performance (Box 45)
  - Item 14: CD, June 8, 1975 performance (Box 45)
  - Item 15: CD, January 24, 1976 performance (Box 45)
  - Item 16: CD, April 9, 1976 performance (Box 45)
  - Item 17: CD, May 28, 1976 performance (Box 45)
  - Items 18-19: CDs, January 21, 1977 performance (Box 45)
  - Item 20: CD, March 5, 1977 performance (Box 45)
  - Item 21: CD, April 22, 1977 performance (Box 45)
  - Item 22: CD, April 29, 1977 performance (Box 45)
  - Items 23-24: CDs, January 20, 1978 performance (Box 45)
  - Item 25: CD, March 3 1978 performance (Box 45)
  - Items 26-27: CDs, April 14, 1978 performance (Box 45)
  - Item 1: CD, May 25, 1978 performance (Box 46)
  - Item 2: CD, March 9, 1979 performance (Box 46)
  - Items 3-4: CDs, April 20, 1979 performance (Box 46)
  - Item 5: CD, February 29, 1980 performance (Box 46)
  - Items 6-7: CDs, March 10, 1980 performance (Box 46)
  - Items 8-9: CDs, April 24, 1981 performance (Box 46)
  - Items 10-11: CDs, January 22, 1982 performance (Box 46)
  - Item 12: CD, April 22, 1983 performance (Box 46)
  - Item 13: CD, May 27, 1983 performance (Box 46)
  - Item 14: CD, October 19, 1983 performance (Box 46)
  - Item 15: CD, February 10, 1984 performance (Box 46)
  - Item 16: CD, March 2, 1984 performance (Box 46)
  - Item 17: CD, March 2, 1984 performance (Box 46)
  - Item 18: CD, May 18, 1984 performance (Box 46)
  - Items 19-20: CDs, January 18, 1985 performance (Box 46)
  - Item 21: CD, May 19, 1985 performance (Box 46)
  - Item 22: CD, March 6, 1987 performance (Box 46)
  - Item 23: CD, October 4, 1987 performance (Box 46)
  - Item 2: Beta Video, October 21, 1984 performance (Box 47)
  - Item 3: Beta Video, January 18, 1985 performance (Box 47)
  - Item 4: Beta Video, April 12, 1984 performance (Box 47)
  - Item 5: Beta Video, February 1, 1987 performance (Box 47)
  - 7-inch Reel-to-Reel Tape: Allanbrook, Douglas – "A Game for Two, undated (Box 48)
  - 7-inch Reel-to-Reel Tape: Antoniou, Theodor – Violin Concerto, undated (Box 48)
  - 7-inch Reel-to-Reel Tape: Antoniou, Theodor – Epilogue; Jeux, undated (Box 48)
  - 7-inch Reel-to-Reel Tape: Antoniou, Theodor – Kinesis, undated (Box 48)
  - 7-inch Reel-to-Reel Tape: Antoniou, Theodor – Kontakion; Dialogues, undated (Box 48)
  - 7-inch Reel-to-Reel Tape: Boone, Charles – Second Landscape; Linea Meridiana; San Zeno/Verona, undated (Box 48)
  - 7-inch Reel-to-Reel Tape: Brief, Todd – Concert Etude; Fantasy for Violin and Piano; Moments, undated (Box 48)
  - 7-inch Reel-to-Reel Tape: Brief, Todd – Cantares, undated (Box 48)
  - 7-inch Reel-to-Reel Tape: Cantrick, Robert B. – Local, undated (Box 48)
  - 7-inch Reel-to-Reel Tape: Chicago Symphony Orchestra in Mandel Hall, July 9, 1967 [1 of 2] (Box 48)
  - 7-inch Reel-to-Reel Tape: Chicago Symphony Orchestra in Mandel Hall, July 9, 1967 [2 of 2] (Box 48)
  - 7-inch Reel-to-Reel Tape: Contemporary Chamber Players Rehearsal, January 18, 1970 (Box 48)
  - 7-inch Reel-to-Reel Tape: Cook, Barbara (in Concert) [1 of 2] (Box 48)
  - 7-inch Reel-to-Reel Tape: Cook, Barbara (in Concert) [2 of 2] (Box 48)
  - 7-inch Reel-to-Reel Tape: Dashow, James – A Way of Staying, 1978 (Box 48)
  - 7-inch Reel-to-Reel Tape: Druckman, Jacob – String Quartet #2, circa 1966 (Box 49)
  - 7-inch Reel-to-Reel Tape: Epstein, Alvin – The Man with the Blue Guitar; Dialogue for Flute and Percussion, undated (Box 49)
  - 7-inch Reel-to-Reel Tape: Erb, D. – Mirage, undated (Box 49)
  - 7-inch Reel-to-Reel Tape: Fox, Fred – Beyond Winterlock, 1977 (Box 49)
  - 7-inch Reel-to-Reel Tape: Ghent, Emmanuel (no title), undated (Box 49)
  - 7-inch Reel-to-Reel Tape: Gressel, Joel – Joint Resolution, 1980 (Box 49)
  - 7-inch Reel-to-Reel Tape: Jolas, Betsy – Quatuor II; Trio à Cordes Français, undated (Box 49)
  - 7-inch Reel-to-Reel Tape: Koplow, Philip – The String Quartet in Time of Vietnamization, undated (Box 49)
  - 7-inch Reel-to-Reel Tape: Bo Lawergren – Piano Concerto, undated (Box 49)
  - 7-inch Reel-to-Reel Tape: Lerdahl, Fred – Aftermath, 1973 (Box 49)
  - 7-inch Reel-to-Reel Tape: Levine, Jeffrey – Electronic Material for Chamber Setting II, undated (Box 49)
  - 7-inch Reel-to-Reel Tape: Levine, Jeffrey – Second Movement Material for Chamber Setting II, undated (Box 49)
  - 7-inch Reel-to-Reel Tape: Lieberman, Glenn – Dialectic; Metalwork; Ei Qui Tympanum Pulsat: In Memoriam; Termini, circa 1978 (Box 49)
  - 7-inch Reel-to-Reel Tape: London, Edwin – Portraits of 3 Ladies (American), undated (Box 49)
  - 7-inch Reel-to-Reel Tape: Pelosi, Louis – A Cummings Pastorale, circa 1978 (Box 50)
  - 7-inch Reel-to-Reel Tape: Pelosi, Louis – Seven Interventions for Piano, circa 1980 (Box 50)
  - 7-inch Reel-to-Reel Tape: Perkins – Piece for 13 Instruments, undated (Box 50)
  - 7-inch Reel-to-Reel Tape: Perle, George – Serenade III, 1983 (Box 50)
  - 7-inch Reel-to-Reel Tape: Ronsheim, John Richard – Composition for 27 Instruments, undated (Box 50)
  - 7-inch Reel-to-Reel Tape: Ronsheim, John Richard – Soliliquio per 27 Strumenti, undated (Box 50)
  - 7-inch Reel-to-Reel Tape: Schafer, R. Murray – Gita, circa 1967 (Box 50)
  - 7-inch Reel-to-Reel Tape: Schafer, R. Murray – Requiems for the Party Girl, circa 1966 (Box 50)
  - 7-inch Reel-to-Reel Tape: Schafer, R. Murray (no title), undated (Box 50)
  - 7-inch Reel-to-Reel Tape: Shapey, Ralph – Incantations for Soprano and 10 Instruments, undated (Box 50)
  - 7-inch Reel-to-Reel Tape: Shinohara, Makoto – Visions II; Alterivances, circa 1970 (Box 50)
  - 7-inch Reel-to-Reel Tape: Smiley, Pril – Eclipse; Kolyonsa, 1975 (Box 50)
  - 7-inch Reel-to-Reel Tape: Stilman-Lasansky, Julia – Barcarola, undated (Box 50)
  - 7-inch Reel-to-Reel Tape: von Wrochem, Klaus – Streichquartett für 6, 1968 (Box 50)
  - 7-inch Reel-to-Reel Tape: Weinberg, Henry – Movement for String Quartet, undated (Box 51)
  - 7-inch Reel-to-Reel Tape: Yarden, Elie – Eros & Psyche, 1971 (Box 51)
  - 7-inch Reel-to-Reel Tape: Unknown – Confluence, undated (Box 51)
  - 7-inch Reel-to-Reel Tape: Unknown (no title), undated (Box 51)
  - 5-inch Reel-to-Reel Tape: Michael Barolsky – Cries and Whispers, undated (Box 51)
  - 5-inch Reel-to-Reel Tape: Michael Barolsky – Dakar; Cries and Whispers, undated (Box 51)
  - 5-inch Reel-to-Reel Tape: Clive? – Speculum, undated (Box 51)
  - 5-inch Reel-to-Reel Tape: Davidovsky, Mario – Synchronisms No. 3, undated (Box 51)
  - 5-inch Reel-to-Reel Tape: Eaton, John – Ajax, 1972 (Box 51)
  - 5-inch Reel-to-Reel Tape: Fleischer, Robert – Duos for Violin and Cello; Cantabile and Melody; Vocalise #2; Serenade Op. 2; Spanish Dance, undated (Box 51)
  - 5-inch Reel-to-Reel Tape: Hoffmann, Richard – Orchestra Piece; Piano Quartet, undated (Box 51)
  - 5-inch Reel-to-Reel Tape: Karlins, M. William – Quartet No. 2, 1976 (Box 51)
  - 5-inch Reel-to-Reel Tape: Lewis, R. H. – Combinazioni III; Osservazioni I, undated (Box 51)
  - 5-inch Reel-to-Reel Tape: Okasaka Keiki – Iriai, undated (Box 52)
  - 5-inch Reel-to-Reel Tape: Panetti, Joan – Madrigali, 1974 (Box 52)
  - 5-inch Reel-to-Reel Tape: Suderburg, Robert – Cantata #2, undated (Box 52)
  - Couper, Monroe – Fossils for Clarinet and Piano – Cassette Tape, Correspondence, 1985 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Grahn, Ulf – Du Silence; A Clear Midnight; Soundscape III; Sonata: Regicus of Time – Cassette Tape, Correspondence, 1980 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Hyla, Lee – Pre-Pulse Suspended – Cassette Tape, Correspondence, 1984 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Winsor, Phil – Melted Ears; Conflations; Coronation; Orgel – 7-inch Reel-to-Reel Tape, Score, CV, circa 1967 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Cassette Tape: Antoniou, Theodor – Chamber Selections, undated (Box 53)
  - Cassette Tape: Asia, Daniel – Music of Daniel Asian, undated (Box 53)
  - Cassette Tape: Asia, Daniel – Ossabow Island Dreams; Rivalries, undated (Box 53)
  - Cassette Tape: Bazelon – Fusions, undated (Box 53)
  - Cassette Tape: Carl – Surge, Sunburst, circa 1987 (Box 53)
  - Cassette Tape: Dickman, Steven – String Quartet, 1978 (Box 53)
  - Cassette Tape: Duggar, Edwin – Two Rhapsodies, circa 1991 (Box 53)
  - Cassette Tape: Eckert, Michael – Three Poems of Emily Dickinson; Three Songs from the Chinese; Piano Variations, undated (Box 53)
  - Cassette Tape: Fulkerson, Christopher – Works, undated (Box 53)
  - Cassette Tape: Gilboa, Jacob – Three Vocalises for Peter Breughel, undated (Box 53)
  - Cassette Tape: Gilboa, Jacob – Vocalises; 3 Red Sea Impressions, undated (Box 53)
  - Cassette Tape: Henze – La Miracle de la Rose, undated (Box 53)
  - Cassette Tape: Keats, Donald – Dialogue for Piano and Winds; Musica Instrumentalis I, undated (Box 53)
  - Cassette Tape: Kiroff, Matthew -- Balang, 1986 (Box 53)
  - Cassette Tape: Lam Bun-Ching – After Spring; Lü, undated (Box 53)
  - Cassette Tape: Lawergren, Bo – Tape for Concerto for Piano, Segment 3, undated (Box 53)
  - Cassette Tape: Lees, Benjamin – Collage, undated (Box 53)
  - Cassette Tape: Lerdahl, Fred – Fantasy Etudes, 1985 (Box 54)
  - Cassette Tape: Liptak, David – Chamber Concerto no. 1; Chamber Concerto no. 2; Timepiece, undated (Box 54)
  - Cassette Tape: MacBride – Xyways, 1985 (Box 54)
  - Cassette Tape: Maw, Nicholas – The Voice of Love; La Vita Nuova, undated (Box 54)
  - Cassette Tape: Moss, L. – Music of Changes, 1987 (Box 54)
  - Cassette Tape: Payne, Anthony – The Stones and Lonely Places Sing, undated (Box 54)
  - Cassette Tape: Reise, Jay – Concerto Fantasy; Cello Fantasy, undated (Box 54)
  - Cassette Tape: Reise, Jay – Symphonies 1 & 2, undated (Box 54)
  - Cassette Tape: Rosenblum, Matthew – Harp Quartet; Le Jow Ra, undated (Box 54)
  - Cassette Tape: Saxton, Robert – Canzona, undated (Box 54)
  - Cassette Tape: Susman, William – Trailing Vortices, circa 1986 (Box 54)
  - Cassette Tape: Tal – Imago, undated (Box 54)
  - Cassette Tape: Thomas, Augusta Read – and quiet hides the horizon, undated (Box 54)
  - Cassette Tape: Thorne, Summer's Saraband, undated (Box 54)
  - Cassette Tape: Vermeer String Quartet, October 28, 1994 (Box 54)
- Series XV: Restricted
  This series contains financial and administrative records restricted for 50 years from the date of creation, and evaluative material restricted for 80 years.
  - Budgets and Financial Records (R-50), 1965-1969 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Contracts and Payroll (R-50), 1965-1969 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence – Personnel (R-50), 1967-1987 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Budgets and Financial Records (R-50), 1970-1976 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Payroll (R-50), 1971-1975 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Contracts and Payroll (R-50), 1976-1980 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Budgets and Financial Records (R-50), 1979-1987 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Account Ledger (R-50), 1978-1983 (Box 56)
  - Contracts and Payroll (R-50), 1981-1986 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Fellowship Audition Evaluations (R-80) [1 of 2], 1967-1972 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Fellowship Audition Evaluations (R-80) [2 of 2], 1967-1972 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Evaluative Material – Students (R-80), 1969-1980 (Box 57, Folder 3)